beastnode.com 2019-08-23

# Minecraft Server Hosting | BeastNode: Performance Server Hosting & VPS Hosting - Privacy Policy

#####  Updated May 24, 2018

* * *

**Definitions:**

‘Personal Data’ means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.

‘User’ means the individual using our service who is the subject of Personal Data.

‘Data Controller’ means the natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of personal data.

‘Data Processor’ means a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes personal data on behalf of the controller.

‘Recipient’ means a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or another body, to which the personal data are disclosed, whether a third party or not.

‘Third party’ means a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or body other than the data subject, controller or processor.

**What type of data do we collect and process?**

We collect a variety of data in order to provide our services to you.

Examples of data collected:

  1. Full name
  2. Email address
  3. Address, state, province, zip/postal code, and country
  4. Site cookies (related to BeastNode content only)
  5. IP Address

The use of this data will be used for email based promotional content and review invitations. Either of the above forms of contact can be stopped and removed by unsubscribing which can easily be found at the bottom of such emails.

The use of your IP (Internet Protocol) address will be used for security and verification of account ownership along with website tracking to examine how our customers navigate pages. If you no longer wish to participate tracking can be disabled via your browser configuration.

Site Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  1. To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  2. To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  3. To process transactions (Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.)

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Data Processors we work with:**

PayPal (https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full)  
Payment Processor

Authorize.Net (https://www.authorize.net/company/privacy/)  
Payment Processor

TrustPilot (https://legal.trustpilot.com/end-user-privacy-terms)  
Customer Satisfaction Processor

SingleHOP: (https://www.singlehop.com/legal/privacy-policy/)  
Service Provider

Google:  
Google Analytics:  
The use of Google Analytics is entirely anonymous with the intention of tracking users throughout our website to better understand how users navigate our website.   
Their Privacy Policy is available here: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/  
Google GSuite:  
https://policies.google.com/privacy

**Data Storage Terms**

Your personal information will only be stored for as long as it required for the applicable laws and regulations we adhere to.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act).

**Privacy of Children**

We do not aim to address users under the age of 18 (Categorised as “Children” or “Child”).

Collection of personal data of any Child is unknowingly submitted to us. Children must seek parental or guardian permission before using our services and made aware of the collection of said personal data.

In the event information of a Child has been collected without Parental or Guardian consent it will be removed immediately from all forms media within our systems.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline as we do not collect any information offline.

**Terms and Conditions of Service**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at the Terms of Service

**Your Rights**

At any time you may commit the following:  

  * Amend your personal data (Name(s), Address and Phone Number).

You may request the following under certain conditions:  

  * Request removal of any Personal Data we hold on you.
  * Request submission to a Third Party Acting on your behalf.
  * Request delivery of any Personal Data directly to you.

**Your Consent**

By using this service, you hereby agree to the collection and use of such information following within this privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on May, 2018.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may [Contact Us](https://www.beastnode.com/r/contact)
